As long as modern-day crimes involve people,
طالما جرائم العصر الحديث تتضمّن بشراً
there are no unsolvable mysteries!
!لا توجد ألغاز لا تُحلّ
Today's guests are super special!
!ضيوف اليوم مميّزون جداً
Relationships can be complex things!
!يمكن للعلاقات البشرية أن تكون معقّدة
He sees the single truth for what it is,
يرى الحقيقة الواحدة
and looks like a kid but has the mind of an adult!
يحمل مظهر طفل، لكنّ عقله عقل بالغ
His name? Detective Conan!
!اسمه المتحرّي كونان
The Ojamanbo Murder Case
جريمة قتل أوجامانبو
Sunday, 7:00 a.m.
الأحد، السابعة صباحاً
Come on, Dad!
!أسرع يا أبي
Are you worn out already?
هل أصابك الإنهاك بهذه السرعة؟
Don't blame me, blame my hangover...
ليس بيدي، فلا أزال أعاني أثر الشراب
He's the one who suggested it in the first place...
كنتَ من اقترح خروجنا في المقام الأوّل
Yeah. We just came along...
صحيح، رافقناك فحسب
Okay, only two more kilometers to the park!
!هيّا، تبقّى كيلومتران فحسب للحديقة
Come on, you can do it!
!هيّا، اجتهد
Let's take a break for a minute...
...مهلك، لنسترح قليلاً يا ران
Ojamanbo Cleaning Company, Eastern Business Director, Tsunehisa Fujii (27)
(فوجي تسونيهيسا (27 مدير الأعمال الشرقية لشركة أوجامانبو للتنظيف
What's this?
ما هذا؟
Over here!
!هنا
You two stay here!
!ابقيا هنا
Ojamanbo Cleaning Company, President, Hideyuki Nakayama (29)
(ناكاياما هيديوكي (29 رئيس شركة أوجامانبو للتنظيف
Asagi-san! Asagi-san!
!أساغي-سان! أساغي-سان
Ojamanbo Cleaning Company, President's Secretary, Kuniko Asagi (31)
(أساغي كونيكو (31 سكرتيرة رئيس شركة أوجامانبو للتنظيف
Yes? Is something the matter, sir?
أجل، أهناك خطبٌ ما سيّدي؟
It appears something happened outside.
يبدو أنّ أمراً وقع في الخارج
Could you go take a look for me?
هلّا تفقدتِ الأمر؟
Yes, of course.
حاضر، بالطبع
Hey, call an ambulance!
!اطلبوا الإسعاف
This looks bad!
!يبدو هذا سيّئاً
It's the same drawing as that truck's.
نفس الرسمة على تلك الشاحنة
He's dead.
إنّه ميت
It looks like that iron girder fell on him from above...
يبدو أنّ العارضة الحديدية سقطت من الأعلى
Neither of the buildings have windows.
لا نوافذ بأيّ من البنائين
Meaning this girder fell from the roof?
ما يعني أنّ هذه العارضة سقطت من السقف؟
Who are you?
من أنتم؟
We were cleaning the building across the street--
كنّا ننظف البناية مقابل الشارع
we're from Ojamanbo.
نحن من أوجامانبو
Sorry to ask, but could you check out this abandoned building?
المعذرة، لكن هلّا تفقدتم هذا المبنى المهجور؟
Someone might have dropped the girder from it.
ربما أسقط أحدهم العارضة منه
Right!
!حسناً
Oh? Those are our--
...ماذا؟ أولئك
It's just my luck that I'd run into a big incident
يا لحظّي لأصادف حادثةً كهذه
first thing Sunday morning...
في صباح الأحد
Fujii-san!
!فوجي-سان
You know him?!
تعرفينه؟
Yes! He's one of our company's directors!
!أجل! إنّه أحد مدراء شركتنا
But why?
لكن لمَ؟
So Fujii-san was on his way from his office up ahead
كان فوجي-سان في طريقه من المكتب هناك
to the main office here?
إلى هذا المكتب الرئيسي إذاً؟
Yes. He was supposed to meet the company president at 9:00.
أجل، كان يُفترض أن يلتقي الرئيس عند التاسعة
Oh, that's right! I need to inform him about this!
!صحيح، عليّ إخباره
Sir!
!حضرة الرئيس
Asagi-san. What happened?
أساغي-سان، ماذا حصل؟
It's Director Fujii...
إنّه المدير فوجي
Did something happen to him?
أحلّ أمرٌ به؟
Fujii!
!فوجي
Asagi-san!
!أساغي-سان
Move the Manbo Mobile away from that building right away!
انقلي شاحنة مانبو !من المبنى المقابل فوراً
It'll be in the way when the police get here! Hurry!
!ستعترض الطريق عند وصول الشرطة، أسرعي
Right!
!حسناً
But why did this happen?
لكن لمَ حصل هذا؟
Come on in.
تفضّلوا
What's that switch for?
ما وظيفة ذاك المفتاح؟
Now, then. When the incident occurred,
،إذاً، عندما وقعت الحادثة
Nakayama-san was in this room,
كانا ناكاياما-سان في هذه الغرفة
and Asagi-san was in the room next door. Right?
وأنت يا أساغي-سان في الغرفة المجاورة، صحيح؟
Yes.
أجل
Is there anyone who can vouch for this?
أهناك من يشهد على ذلك؟
Sorry?
...قصدك
The truth is, right after the incident,
في الواقع، بعد الحادثة
Mori-kun here asked your employees to inspect
طلب موري-كن هنا من موظّفيكم البحث
the abandoned building next door.
في البناية المجاورة المهجورة
Yes, so I've heard.
سمعتُ بذلك
But they didn't find anyone suspicious, right?
لكنّهم لم يجدوا أيّ شيء مشبوه، صحيح؟
Nope.
بالفعل
But when I thought hard about it,
،لكن عندما أمعنتُ التفكير
I realized there's also a high possibility
أدركتُ وجود احتمال لسقوط العارضة
the iron girder was dropped from the roof of this building.
من سطح هذا المبنى
Floors 3 and up belong to a parent company.
الطابق الثالث فما فوق من هذا المبنى يخصّ الشركة المالكة
I hear floors 1 and 2 are being rented out to your company.
سمعتُ أنّ الطابقين الأوّل والثاني مؤجران لشركتكم
And from what the security guard told us,
،ومما أخبرنا به حارس الأمن
the parent company above you is closed because it's Sunday.
كانت الشركة المالكة مغلقة بما أنّ اليوم عطلة أسبوع
Other than Nakayama-san and Asagi-san,
فباستثناء ناكاياما-سان وأساغي-سان
nobody had entered this building.
لم يدخل أحد هذا المبنى
That's what he said.
هذا ما قاله
So you want to know our alibis?
تريد معرفة حجّة غيابنا إذاً؟
I don't know what to say.
...هذه مشكلة
There wasn't anyone else to vouch for us...
فلم يكن هناك من يشهد لنا
This switch is--
...هذا المفتاح
I can see the road out front!
!يمكنني رؤية الشارع الأمامي
Judging from this angle, there must be a camera on the roof!
بناءً من هذه الزاوية، فلا بدّ أن هناك كاميرا على السطح
It's recording!
إنّها تسجّل
Now I see! The camera's angle changes automatically!
فهمت! تتغيّر زاوية الكاميرا آلياً
Which means that when it's on manual
ما يعني أنّه عندما تُضبط على الوضع اليدوي
you use this stick to change the angle...
تستعمل هذه العصا لتغيير الزاوية
Hey, you! Don't touch other people's things!
!أنت! لا تلمس أغراض الآخرين
Is this your wife, Nakayama-san?
أهذه زوجتك يا ناكاياما-سان؟
No, that's my sister.
كلا، أختي
Your sister?
أختك؟
Yes. But she passed away this January...
أجل، لكنّها تُوفيت في يناير هذا العام
Dad!
!أبي
I'm sorry to hear that...
...يؤسفني سماع ذلك
But becoming a company president at such a young age...
لكن وصولك لمنصب رئيس شركة في هذا العمر اليافع
That's really something!
أمر مبهر بحق
This company was originally just me, Fujii, and my sister Kumiko
كانت هذه الشركة تحتويني أنا وفوجي وأختي كوميكو فحسب
back in my college days.
من أيامي في الجامعة
We originally started it as a "jack-of-all-trades" shop.
أسسناها كشركة متنوّعة الأعمال
We came up with the name "Ojamanbo"
"خطر لنا اسم "أوجامانبو
because we would actively go to random homes and demand work.
لأنّنا نذهب لمنازل الناس عشوائياً ونعرض عليهم تنفيذ أيّ عمل لهم
I see.
فهمت
But to our delight, the business did much better than we ever expected.
لكن ما سرّنا هو أنّ عملنا ازدهر أكثر مما توقّعنا
Two years later, we took our first step into cleaning
وبعد عامين، خطونا خطوتنا الأولى في التنظيف
by creating the Ojamanbo Cleaning Company.
بتأسيس شركة تنظيف أوجامانبو
I took the role of company president,
تقلدتُ منصب رئيس الشركة
and Fujii oversaw work as business director of the eastern region.
وأشرف فوجي على العمل في منصب مدير أعمال المنطقة الشرقية
My sister worked as my secretary,
بينما عملت أختي كسكرتيرتي
but she died in an accident in January.
لكنّها ماتت في حادث في يناير
Inspector.
حضرة المفتّش
I'll tell you since you'd eventually find out anyway,
سأخبرك بما أنّك ستكتشف بالتحقيق بأيّ حال
there was some trouble between me and Fujii.
كانت هناك مشاكل بيني وفوجي
Trouble?
مشاكل؟
Fujii was going to start his own cleaning company by himself.
كان فوجي سيؤسس شركة تنظيفه الخاصة
Because of this, he tried to take several highly-skilled employees
لذا حاول أخذ عدد من موظّفينا المهرة
along with him, so...
...للعمل معه، فكنّا
Whenever we met, we always clashed with each other.
نتشاجر كلّما التقينا
I was supposed to talk with Fujii again today.
كان يُفترض أن أتكلم مع فوجي مُجدداً اليوم
I got it!
!اكتشفتُ الأمر
You already figured it out?!
بـ-بهذه السرعة؟
Nakayama-san was the one who dropped the girder from the roof!
كان ناكاياما-سان من أسقط !العارضة من سطح المبنى
Asagi-san and Nakayama-san are lovers,
أساغي-سان وناكاياما-سان حبيبان
so she's lying to cover for him!
!لذا هي تكذب للتغطية عليه
What's so funny?
ما-ما الذي يدعو للضحك؟
As if he and I would ever be lovers!
مُحال أن أكون أنا والرئيس حبيبين
Sorry, but you're wrong, Mori-san.
آسف، لكنّك مخطئ يا موري-سان
The reason being that she's getting married next month!
فهي ستتزوّج الشهر المقبل
Married?
تتزوّج؟
Inspector!
حضرة المفتّش
It wasn't much, but we found a mark made by an iron girder
كان خفيفاً، لكن وجدنا أثر من عارضة معدنية
on the roof of the building next door.
على سطح المبنى المهجور المجاور
What?!
!ماذا؟
So the girder fell from the roof of the abandoned building!
سقطت العارضة من سطح !المبنى المهجور إذاً
We also found this harmonica lying next to the body...
وجدنا هذه الهارمونيكا بجوار الجثّة أيضاً
His name's on it, so it would seem it belongs to Fujii-san...
اسمه عليها، فيبدو أنّها كانت تخصّ فوجي-سان
Yes, that's his.
تلك له بالفعل
I've seen it on several occasions.
فقد رأيتُها عدّة مرات
However, we couldn't find any fingerprints on it at all.
لكننا لم نجد أيّ بصمات عليها
It's clean, almost as if it had been wiped with a cloth.
إنّها نظيفة كما لو مُسحت بقطعة قماش
If it belongs to Fujii-san, shouldn't his fingerprints be on it?
إذا كانت تخصّ فوجي-سان، أفلا يُفترض أن تكون بصماته عليها؟
Yes, but...
...أجل، لكن
I just remembered some unimportant business.
المعذرة، تذكّرتُ عملاً صغيراً
Would you mind if I leave for just a bit?
هل تمانعون خروجي قليلاً؟
No, that would be fine.
كلا، البتّة
Thank you.
شكراً
Asagi-san. Contact Fujii-kun's parents and fiancée.
أساغي-سان، اتّصلي بوالديّ فوجي-كن وخطيبته
Right!
حسناً
Fujii-san has a fiancée?
لفوجي-سان خطيبة؟
Yes. Apparently she's the daughter of a wealthy man,
أجل، يبدو أنّها ابنة رجل ثريّ
and the start-up funds for his new company
ورأس مال تأسيس شركته الجديدة
were supposed to come from him.
كان سيأتي منه وفقما يبدو
Say, how did Nakayama-san's sister die?
أخبريني، كيف ماتت أخت ناكاياما-سان؟
She was in an accident.
كانت حادثة
An accident?
حادثة؟
Yes.
أجل
Apparently she had a big argument with her brother
يبدو أنّها خاضت شجاراً شديداً مع أخيها
and quit in December.
واستقالت في ديسمبر العام الفائت
I was hired as her replacement.
وتمّ تعييني مكانها
and was hit in the head by an iron girder on a construction site.
وسقطت عليها عارضة حديدية على الرأس في موقع البناء
Come again?!
ماذا؟
That's exactly the same as what happened this morning!
!هذا كحادثة صباح اليوم تماماً
That's why I've been thinking about how terrible coincidences can be...
...لذا كنتُ أفكّر برعب المصادفات أحياناً
Was it really a coincidence, though?
أكانت مصادفة حقّاً؟
Could his sister's death have some relevance
أيمكن أنّ لموت أخته
to the truth behind this incident?
علاقة ما بهذه الحادثة؟
If so, then it's highly likely that Nakayama-san did it!
في تلك الحالة، يُرجّح جدّاً أن ناكاياما-سان كان الفاعل
But how?!
لكن كيف؟
At any rate, I'm going to re-question the employees
بأيّ حال، سأعيد استجواب العمّال
who were cleaning the building across the street.
الذين كانوا ينظّفون البناية المقابلة
You folks stay here.
ابقوا هنا
Understood.
حسناً
Let's go.
هيّا، لنذهب
Yes, sir!
!حاضر
After entering this room, Nakayama-san switched the camera to Auto.
بعد دخوله هذه الغرفة، غيّر ناكاياما-سان وضعية الكاميرا للآلية
If he's the killer, then it must be the key to something!
إذا كان القاتل، فلا بدّ أن ذلك مفتاح لشيء
I can see the road out front! This is neat!
!يمكنني رؤية الطريق المقابل! هذا رائع
Oh, a security camera on the roof is recording that.
هذا تسجيل كاميرا مراقبة على السطح
A security camera?
كاميرا مراقبة؟
Yes. The company president is always checking the monitor
أجل، يتفقّد رئيس الشركة الشاشة دوماً
to make sure there's no litter on the street in front of the building.
للتأكد من عدم وجود قمامة على الشارع مقابل المبنى
I see. So it's the policy of the president of a cleaning company.
فهمت، هذه سياسة رئيس شركة تنظيف
Yes. His concepts are always unique--
أجل، أفكاره فريدة دوماً
the Manbo Mobile was his idea too!
شاحنة مانبو كانت فكرته أيضاً
Parking it in front of a spotless building makes for great publicity!
ركنها أمام مبنى لامع النظافة يشكّل إعلاناً ممتازاً
Say, this is set on Auto,
هذه مضبوطة على الوضع الآلي
but do you think we could see inside that alley if it was on Manual?
لكن أيمكننا رؤية ذاك الزقاق إن بدّلناها لليدوي؟
I'm not sure. Why don't you try and see?
لستُ متأكدة، لمَ لا تجرب؟
Okay!
حسناً
Can't see it at all, huh?
لا يمكننا رؤيته أبداً
No.
أجل
What's this strap?
ما هذا الشريط؟
Binoculars?!
منظار؟
Conan-kun!
!كونان-كن
You know better than to open other people's drawers!
!لا يصحّ بك فتح أدراج الآخرين
I'm gonna go up to the roof!
!سأذهب للسطح قليلاً
So that's the security camera.
هذه كاميرا المراقبة إذاً
It's pretty big...
إنّها كبيرة الحجم
The abandoned building next door is one floor shorter than this one...
البناية المهجورة المقابلة أقصر بطابق من هذه
That must be the mark made by the sliding iron girder.
لا بدّ أن ذاك الأثر الذي تركه انزلاق العارضة الحديدة
This height difference would make it impossible
فرق الارتفاع هذا يمنع العودة
to return the girder up here if it had been lowered
للمبنى المرتفع بعد إسقاط العارضة
onto the abandoned building.
من المبنى المنخفض
Which means Nakayama-san couldn't have dropped it--
معنى ذلك لا يمكن لناكاياما-سان إسقاط العارضة
he was inside this building.
بما أنّه كان في هذا المبنى
Plus, he was in his office when it happened!
كما أنّه كان في مكتبه وقت الحادثة
Wait a minute! It's possible that--
...لحظة، أيمكن
Here we go!
ها هو
It's not much, but there's a fresh scratch mark here
إنّه خفيف، لكن يوجد أثر خدش حديث
from something thin!
!من شيء رفيع
There's no doubt about it!
لا شكّ في الأمر
Using this method, it would be possible to drop the girder
سيمكنه إسقاط العارضة حتّى من مكتبه
even from his office!
باستعمال هذه الطريقة
But how did he know Fujii-san was in the alley?!
لكن كيف عرف أنّ فوجي-سان كان في الزقاق؟
Wait!
...أيمكن
No good.
كلا
None of the lower floors reflect what's in the alley!
لا شيء من الطوابق السفلية يعكس ما بالزقاق
Was it really impossible for Nakayama-san to have done it?!
أكان مستحيلاً على ناكاياما-سان ارتكاب الجريمة حقّاً؟
Conan-kun?
كونان-كن؟
What are you doing?
ما الذي تفعله؟
Nothing really...
...لا-لا شيء
Wait! Come to think of it...
...لحظة، كما أذكر
Asagi-san!
!أساغي-سان
Move the Manbo Mobile away from that building right away!
انقلي شاحنة مانبو !من المبنى المقابل فوراً
Now I see!
!فهمت الآن
That's why the harmonica didn't have any fingerprints on it!
!لهذا لم تتواجد أيّ بصمات على الهارمونيكا
Nakayama-san really did do it!
!كان الفاعل ناكاياما-سان حقّاً
How'd it go, Inspector?
كيف مضى الأمر حضرة المفتّش؟
Not well.
لا نتائج
Apparently they had finished their window-cleaning
يبدو أنّهم أنهوا تنظيف النوافذ
and moved on to cleaning the first floor when it happened.
وانتقلوا لتنظيف الطابق الأول عندما وقعت الحادثة
They said they didn't see anything.
قالوا أنّهم لم يروا شيئاً
I see...
هكذا إذاً
Darn it!
...تبّاً
Will checking this video prove
هل ستثبت مجرّد مراجعة التسجيل
that he controlled the only camera on the roof?!
أنّه حرّك الكاميرا الوحيدة على السطح؟
But will that alone...
...لكن أيكفي ذلك
...serve as conclusive proof?!
ليكون دليلاً قاطعاً؟
What's this?!
...هذا
Alright! Now I have evidence!
!حسناً، لديّ الدليل الآن
Sorry to keep you waiting.
أعتذر على الإطالة
Ah, Nakayama-san. You can leave for today.
ناكاياما-سان، انتهينا اليوم
We'll contact you at a later time.
سنتواصل معك في وقت لاحق
I see.
هكذا إذاً
Oh no!
!كلا
This video'll be erased if he notices it!
!سيُمسح هذا التسجيل إن لاحظه ناكاياما-سان
I have no choice! I'll use my usual method!
!لا خيار أمامي، سأستعمل طريقتي المعتادة
What?
ماذا؟
What is it, Mori-kun?
ما الأمر يا موري-كن؟
Inspector. You mustn't let him leave just yet.
حضرة المفتّش، لا يمكن المغادرة بعد
The reason being that I've seen through the superb trick
فقد تبيّنت لي الحيلة الماكرة
Nakayama-san used to murder Fujii-san from this room.
التي استعملها ناكاياما-سان لقتل فوجي-سان من هذه الغرفة
What?!
!ماذا؟
So you're saying Nakayama-san killed him?!
!أتقصد أنّ ناكاياما-سان هو القاتل؟
Yes. The key to his trick was the security camera on the roof.
أجل، مفتاح الحيلة هو كاميرا المراقبة على السطح
The security camera?
كاميرا المراقبة؟
Nakayama-san placed an iron girder on top of the building next door
وضع ناكاياما-سان عارضة حديدية على سطح البناية المجاورة
and then connected it to the security camera with something thin--
ثم ربطها بكاميرا المراقبة بشيء رفيع
piano wire, most likely.
سلك بيانو على الأرجح
Afterward, when Fujii-san walked into the alleyway,
،بعدها، عندما دخل فوجي-سان الزقاق
he operated the security camera,
حرّك كاميرا المراقبة
which had been set to Manual in advance.
التي حوّلها للوضع اليدوي سلفاً
The reason Nakayama-san had Asagi-san check what happened outside
سبب جعله أساغي-سان تتفقد ما حصل بالخارج
was so he could go to the roof
هو كي يصعد للسطح
and remove the piano wire from the camera.
وينزع سلك البيانو من الكاميرا
And the reason he went outside just now
وسبب خروجه قبل قليل
was to dispose of that piano wire.
هو للتخلّص من ذاك السلك
Am I wrong?
ألستُ محقّاً؟
You're not only wrong, but your theory lacks a vital part, Mori-san.
فوق خطئك، فهناك خلل جوهريّ في استنتاجك يا موري-سان
From in here, how could I have known what time
كيف لي أن أعرف وقت دخول فوجي-كن الزقاق
Fujii would be in the alley?
وأنا هنا؟
I agree.
أتفق معه
It would be impossible to drop the girder on Fujii-san
سيكون مستحيلاً إسقاط العارضة على فوجي-سان
if the timing was even a second off.
لو أخطأ التوقيت ولو بثانية
In order to have Fujii-san stop on a specific spot,
،كي يجعل فوجي-سان يقف في نقطة محددة
Nakayama-san stole his harmonica in advance
سرق ناكاياما-سان الهارمونيكا خاصته سلفاً
and placed it in the alley.
ووضعها في الزقاق
He then used his binoculars to see Fujii-san enter the alley.
ثمّ استعمل المنظار لرؤية دخول فوجي-سان الزقاق
How? The alley isn't visible from here!
كيف؟ لا يمكنك رؤية الزقاق من هنا
Inspector. When the incident occurred,
حضرة المفتّش، في وقت وقوع الحادثة
the company's Manbo Mobile was parked
كانت شاحنة مانبو مركونة
in front of a building across the street.
أمام المبنى المقابل
The logo's eye was a mirror.
وعين الشعار كانت مرآة
What?!
!ماذا؟
Do you see now?
أفهمت الآن؟
Nakayama-san used binoculars to view the reflection of the alley
استعمل ناكاياما-سان المنظار لرؤية انعكاس الزقاق
and then dropped the girder.
ثمّ أسقط العارضة
He waited for just the right time...
انتظر اللحظة المناسبة
That's why you had the Manbo Mobile moved
لذا طلبتَ تحريك شاحنة مانبو
right after you saw his body.
فورما رأيت جثّة فوجي-سان
So that the police wouldn't figure out your trick.
كيلا تنتبه الشرطة لحيلتك
But you made a mistake.
لكنّك ارتكبت خطأً
You dropped the girder before Fujii-san had picked up the harmonica.
أسقطتَ العارضة قبل أن يمسك فوجي-سان بالهارمونيكا
That's why his fingerprints weren't on it.
لذا لم تكن بصماته عليها
You were flustered.
تعجّلت
There's no blaming you.
لا يمكن لومك
Because Ran got in your way at the worst possible time.
فقد تدّخلت ران في أسوأ وقت
But you have no proof of this, Mori-san.
لكن لا دليل لديك يا موري-سان
According to your theory, I've already disposed of the piano wire.
وفقاً لاستنتاجك، فقد تخلّصتُ من سلك البيانو سلفاً
But there is proof.
الدليل موجود
After you used the security camera to drop the girder,
بعدما استعملت كاميرا المراقبة لإسقاط العارضة
you changed the camera's angle
غيّرت زاوية الكاميرا
to make it easier to remove the piano wire.
كيف يسهل نزع سلك البيانو
During that time, the camera recorded
آنذاك، سجّلت الكاميرا الانعكاس
the reflection in the glass windows of the opposite building.
في نوافذ البناية المقابلة الزجاجية
It's all yours, Conan!
الباقي لك يا كونان
Everyone gather over here!
!اجتمعوا هنا
Conan-kun?
كونان-كن؟
Watch closely, everyone.
راقبوا جميعاً
See the camera in the glass's reflection?
يمكنكم رؤية الكاميرا في انعكاس النوافذ، صحيح؟
In just a moment...
...بعد قليل
Here!
!هنا
Company president!
!الرئيس
My sister and Fujii were lovers.
كانت أختي على علاقة بفوجي
But Fujii met a rich man's daughter
لكنّ فوجي التقى ابنة رجل ثريّ
and ditched my sister like it was nothing.
وتخلّى عن أختي كما لو كانت نكرة
As a result, my sister quit the company.
استقالت أختي جرّاء ذلك
So it wasn't because you two had an argument?
لم يكن بسبب شجاركما إذاً؟
I thought so, myself.
ذلك ما اعتقدتُه أيضاً
Our parents died when we were very young.
فقد تُوفيّ أبوانا في صغرنا
My sister always saw me as a father-figure,
لطالما اعتبرتني أختي كالأب
but now she was confused,
لكنّها أصبحت مرتبكة
so she quit the company to get away from her brother.
فتركت الشركة للابتعاد من أخيها
That's what I thought, anyway.
ذلك ما ظننتُه
But that wasn't the case...
لكن لم يكن الوضع كذلك
After she died in an accident,
،بعد موتها في الحادثة
I went to her apartment in Yokohama to tend to her belongings.
ذهبت لشقّتها في يوكوهاما لجمع أغراضها
I realized everything then.
أدركتُ كلّ شيء آنذاك
So then you wiped the harmonica and put it in the alley?
لذا مسحت البصمات عن الهارمونيكا ووضعتها في الزقاق؟
If Fujii hadn't dumped her, she wouldn't have died!
!لو لم يهجر فوجي أختي، لما ماتت
I had to make him pay!
!لم أستطع مسامحته
But it certainly is ironic, isn't it?
لكنّ الأمر مثير للسخرية حقّاً
I used the Manbo Mobile's mirror to commit a murder--
استعملتُ مرآة شاحنة مانبو لارتكاب جريمة
and then I was found guilty because of my reflection in those windows.
ثمّ تمت إدانتي لانعكاسي في زجاج النوافذ
And it was no other than your own company
وكانت شركتك بالذات
that polished those windows.
هي من مسح ذاك الزجاج
But of course.
بالطبع
The Ojamanbo Cleaning Company's cleaning techniques
فتقنيات تنظيف شركة أوجامانبو
are the best in the world!
!هي الأفضل في العالم
Brother...
...أخي
I saw the Manbo Mobile go by today.
مرّت أمامي شاحنة مانبو اليوم
It looks like the company's still going even after the president's arrest.
يبدو أنّ الشركة لا تزال تعمل حتّى بعد اعتقال الرئيس
Yeah. But apparently Asagi-san quit.
أجل، لكن يبدو أنّ مساعدته أساغي-سان استقالت
It must have been a real shock to her.
لا بدّ أنّ الأمر صدمها
I wonder what she's doing now?
ما الذي تفعله الآن يا ترى؟
Hello, there!
!مرحباً
I'm Ojamanbo's new announcer, Kuniko Asagi!
!أنا مُذيعة أوجامانبو الجديدة، أساغي كونيكو
I'm honored to be here!
يُشرفني الوجود هنا
What a strong woman...
...يا للمرأة الصلبة
No! She must have found a clue we don't know about yet!
كلا، لا بدّ أنها وجدت دليلاً لا نزال نجهله
Now that you mention it, Ayako-san was acting odd this afternoon...
بالمناسبة، كانت أياكاو-سان تتصرف بغرابة نوعاً ما ظهيرة اليوم
What?!
!مـ-ماذا؟
Don't tell me Ayako-san's in there!
أيمكن أنّ أياكو-سان هناك؟
The Holmes Freak Murder Case (Part 1)
(جريمة قتل مهووس هولمز (الجزء الأوّل
On the next Conan--
في الحلقة القادمة من كونان
Next Conan's Hint:
تلميح الحلقة القادمة
Blanket.
لحاف
Next episode Conan's rival returns.
!يرجع منافس كونان في الحلقة القادمة
Me again?
!ماذا؟! أنا مجدّداً؟
It's not you, Genta.
!ليس أنت